hello
I hope all of you are doing great
[Music]
we started our journey on 15th August
last year towards India's Mission
Electric
EVS back then were thought to be a dream
and look at where we are just 15 months
later
already in the scooter Market EV
penetration is 15 percent
and in many big cities like Bangalore
Delhi Pune Etc
penetration is above 40 percent
that means almost half of all new
scooters sold in these cities are
already Electric
in June last year only 4 000 electric
scooters were sold all across India
in September this year 50 000 electric
scooters were sold across India
India's EV Revolution is racing ahead
and our mission of ensuring all two
wheelers in India are electric by 2025
is absolutely within our site
and over the next 12 months we will
build EV products in all tubular
categories like commuter scooters
motorbikes sports bikes and more to
ensure everyone buying a nice vehicle
today has a much better EV product to
choose from
and once you experience and buy an EV
you're never going back to ice
by the end of 2025 by converting all two
wheelers in India to Electric we will
also make India the largest ev Market in
the world
and today is a major day in this
revolution
and we are making the biggest push yet
towards this mission
stay with us to find out more
let's begin with software
software is the heart of an electric
vehicle
it enables your vehicle with
capabilities it never had before in the
ice era
and already people are loving what our
move OS enables
when you buy an Ola you're also buying
into a lifetime of upgrades that only
make your vehicle better
we launched movers 1 in Jan this year
move us to in June this year and today
we are taking it to the next level with
move os3
no other Auto Company can match the
speed
here take a look at the future
[Music]
all day and night
all day and night all day and night I'll
be up all night
[Music]
my life
thank you
[Music]
live a life to the maximum
all day and night
all day and night all day and night
[Music]
movo S3 is going to take the
capabilities of your Ola S1 to a level
no other vehicle has ever gone
we finally got proximity unlock for you
no need to enter passcodes or even to
pull out your phone
the scooter just senses you close and
unlocks
and if you walk away it locks
this technology is a world first
doesn't exist in any vehicle car auto
wheeler and we've patented it
here take a look
[Music]
foreign
with vacation mode when you go on
vacation so does your S1
your scooter will go into energy
conservation giving it up to 200 days of
battery life
you can now also see who is calling you
on your screen an auto reply that you'll
call back if you're mid-ride
because safety comes first
we've also introduced multiple profiles
on the same scooter
which means if your restaurant is a
shared or a family scooter everybody can
access it easily without sharing PIN
codes or physical keys
when we launched music on move OS 2 we
saw so many of you having fun with your
S1
playing music on it and dancing at
College fests at garbaz and even wedding
bharats
so we decided to build a proper party
mode in move os3
now your scooter will play your favorite
music and all the scooter lights will
sync to the track
it's really quite an experience
[Music]
oh yeah
huh
[Music]
I wanna see you dance
we're also bringing moods widgets and
sounds to move os3
I don't need to say much about this you
can just see it and feel it
what
[Music]
[Applause]
foreign
[Music]
thank you
foreign
allows for hyper charging too
it's one of the most requested features
you will be able to charge up to 50
kilometers in 15 minutes that's almost
three kilometers per minute
we already have 50 plus hyperchargers
all across India and you can view the
live locations of all hyperchargers in
the Ola app and website and finally
we've got a full community Forum in our
app for our fantastic community
foreign
[Music]
experiences with the S1 and plan rights
together
and maybe sometimes I'll also join you
guys for those rights movo S3 will be
open for beta signups from the 25th of
October on our website and the rollout
to all S1 owners will be completed by
early December
we're always listening closely to our
community and today we're launching two
frequently requested accessories for the
S1
a buddy step for passengers who prefer
to sit sideways and a center stand so
parking in small spaces won't be a
problem anymore
you can explore our accessories on the
app and website starting today
and purchases will begin January 2023
we're doing a lot of exploration on how
we can enhance your riding and ownership
experience with accessories that add on
to the core vehicle platform that we've
built
you can expect a lot of interesting
accessories over the next 12 months from
us
and here's a glimpse of one such concept
that I want to share with you today
which really enhances and takes your S1
experience to a different level
this is a custom buddy space organizer
and we'll have a range that will support
your lifestyle choices College
photography maybe even a soft drink
cooler
and this is just a glimpse of what all
we will make possible for you in the
future with the rs1 I'm also personally
very very excited about the range of
accessories we are working on and we'll
reveal them to you over the next few
months
we've also seen our community make their
own t-shirts in their zest and spirit
for riding the S1
so we've taken this opportunity at this
festive time to launch our very first
merchandise line too
[Music]
thank you
our custom teas will be available for
purchase on the app and website starting
today
we've also been hard at work expanding
our Network
we have now opened 50 experience centers
across India and will have more than 200
by March next year
our experience centers have enabled us
to connect directly with so many of you
we've also doubled our service level
locations in India and are now available
in 300 plus cities
we've also doubled the number of service
Vans we have and can proudly say that 90
percent of our customer issues are
resolved within two days
we're now offering free trials on the S1
where you can take it home for 24 hours
and get to experience it better
we'll be rolling this out in 20 cities
today onwards and 40 cities by the 7th
of November
no other auto company has this direct
link with its customers and this link
between us and our community will only
get closer and stronger
[Music]
the S1 has been sold to every corner of
India
and it has traveled to every part of
India including to lay and cardunga
it's now time we take it globally
and we've always been about from India
for the whole world
Nepal is going to be the first country
in this journey and we'll be inviting
you to join us for our first
International launch
details on this to follow soon on your
community Forum so stay tuned
the Ola S1 officially launches in Nepal
by the end of this year
and will launch in Europe and Latin
America early next year
okay to summarize we've launched the
move os3 today our first accessories
expanded our sales and service network
deep into India and now internationally
like I said at the beginning
the time has come for India's Eevee
Revolution to truly become a mass
movement
let's recap the impact S1 has already
created
for this scooter Market in India priced
above 1 lakh rupees with the S1 and the
S1 Pro Ola now has almost a 50 percent
market share
not just in EVS alone but amongst all
scooters sold
take a second to understand how
significant that is
almost one out of two scooters sold in
the premium scooter segment in India is
already an Ola product in just the first
year of our launch
in another few months people will almost
stop buying premium ice scooters
this revolution now needs to be taken to
the mass segment
we need to build a world-class electric
scooter that everybody can afford
let's create this product together in
this table let's put down what our
electric scooter needs to be to totally
Wipe Out the size product fuel required
the ice needs a lot of petrol on the Ola
EV well you can just enjoy the air
running cost the ice will spend about
two and a half to three rupees per
kilometer on the ol iev I mean maybe 25
peso per kilometer annual maintenance of
course it's a nice vehicle it needs
scheduled maintenance it needs a lot of
other oil changes Etc on the Ola EV EVS
don't have any maintenance top speed on
the ice you'll barely touch probably 80
kilometers per hour on the Ola EV well
our S1 Pro touches 115 let's see if we
can get this to touch close to 90
kilometers per hour ride modes on the
eyes if you're happy if it moves on the
Ola IV SN pro has four let's see if we
can put three ride modes into this
reverse mode yeah on the ice you can use
your legs on the Ola IV you press a
button and you go reverse body space
typical eyes you get maybe 18 to 20
liters you can put a helmet maybe three
kgs of aloe also on the Ola AV maybe
about 34 liters you put your helmet you
put the three cages of Aloo you put your
office back you put your chain stuff to
the office party then maybe you're still
left with some more space technology
on the ice have you ever seen any good
software on the Ola EV you have a
companion app multiple profiles music
hands-free calling navigation vacation
mode tamper alert multiple moods party
mode etc etc the ice product that we
just put here will cost you 90 000
rupees on road minimum and let's see
what we have in store for you for the
Ola AV
this is the scooter we all want
and I'm so excited to share this is
exactly what we have built
this is the S1 air
take a look
[Music]
it's built on the same S1 platform so it
has the same beautiful design and
world-class technology
but we've taken it a step further in
every dimension
we've given it a fresh new look with
these beautiful two-tone body colors
across these five colors the two-tone
look is Simply Amazing
to make it sporty extremely energy
efficient and yet affordable we took out
a whopping 25 kg from the S1 Pro
and hence the S1 air weighs only 99 kgs
the typical ice scooter weighs 110 kgs
the Aston air is much lighter faster and
nimbler to handle
we've re-engineered the powertrain and
battery pack 2.
the S on air has a 4.5 kilowatt Hub
motor and a 2.5 kilowatt hour battery
pack
this gives you a top speed of 85
kilometers per hour and 0 to 40 in just
4.3 seconds
and an IDC range of 100 kilometers in
eco mode
it's the perfect Urban Scooter
it retains our signature large 34 liter
body space
the S1 air will come loaded with movo S3
which means technology features like
profiles party mode calling modes the
works and you'll receive all future
movers upgrades
so there you have it India
your everyday anytime scooter just went
from functional to technologically
advanced
and it no longer has a drinking problem
the purchase window will open in
February and delivery will begin in
early April next year
so what's the price finally
you'll be able to buy it at
I'm so so excited with the S1 air we've
accelerated the end of Ice Age by at
least two years if not more
and it's only a matter of time now and
for this Diwali season I want to leave
you with a little something special
that only the S1 can do
here's wishing everyone a very Happy
Diwali and we hope you and your S1
continue to make beautiful memories
together
[Music]
[Applause]
foreign
[Music]